

340, Mokdongseo-ro, Yangcheon-gu, Seoul, 08089, Republic of Korea

□ (+82) 10-9686-8177 | ■ tyoung96@naver.com | ★ taeyoung96.github.io | □ Taeyoung96

"Nothing ventured, nothing gained."

Summary.

This is Taeyoung Kim, who wants to become an autonomous driving or robotics SW engineer. My research interests are Computer Vision and SLAM. I like to take on challenging tasks and I like to grow up with my colleagues around me. That's why I record and share what I did on my Github or Technical Blog. I would like to participate in changing the world with advanced science and technology.

Research Interests

Computer Vision Object Detection, Segmentation, Depth Estimation

SLAM Visual SLAM, Visual Odometry

Education

Kwang Woon University Seoul, S.Korea

B.S. IN SCHOOL OF ROBOTICS

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2022 (Expected)

- Current GPA: 4.07 / 4.50, Current Major GPA: 4.50 / 4.50
- Club: BARAM (Robotics Academic Group) [2020 Staff], DAISY (English Conversation Club) [2019 Spring President]

Work Experience _

Computer Vision Lab @Korea Univ

Seoul, S.Korea

UNDERGRADUATE LAB INTERN (ADVISOR: PROF. SANGPIL KIM) · Research on computer vision using an Event camera Mar. 2021 - Present

KIST(Korea Institute of Science and Technology)

Seoul, S.Korea

STUDENT INTERN (ADVISOR: DR. KANGGEON KIM)

Sep. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- Research on Monocular Depth Estimation
- Participated in KIST disinfect robot (AI Disinfection Robot) project [Video]

Image Process System Lab @Kwang Woon Univ

Seoul, S.Korea

Undergraduate Lab Intern (Advisor: Prof. Donggyu Sim)

Mar. 2020 - Aug. 2020

- · Research on Image Processing based on Deep learning
- · Participated in seminars related to Deep Learning and Image Processing

Publication

INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE

UR2021, Taeyoung Kim, Omer Faruk Ince, JongBeom Baek, Jun-Sik Kim, KangGeon Kim, 2021.3

IEEE

"Denser Monocular SLAM applied Depth Estimation"

DOMESTIC CONFERENCE

KSPC2020, Naseong Kwon, Taeyoung Kim, Subin Kim, Joohyung Byeon, Jongsuk Lee, Donggyu Sim, 2020.9 "Luma Mapping with Chroma Scaling based on CNN feature map for VVC subjective quality improvement"

Honors & Awards

AWARDS

2020.11 Dean's List, for Academic Excellence

KwangWoon Univ. **NAVER CLOUD**

2020.9 **5th Place on B-track**, Korea Health Datathon 2020

KwangWoon Univ.

PLATFORM

2019.10 Dean's List, for Academic Excellence

HONORS

National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship,
for the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

National Science and Engineering Undergraudate Scholarship,

Korea Student Aid
for the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation

To the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation

Foundation

The students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation

The students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation

The students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation

The students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation

The students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation of the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation of the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation of the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation of the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Foundation of the students with excellent grades, those who have been recommended by the university

Skills_

Programming C++/C, Python, JAVA, Matlab **Framework** Pytorch, Tensorflow, Keras

DevOps Git, Docker, ROS **Languages** Korean, English

Extracurricular Activity

Technical Blogs Github blog

WRITERS May. 2020 - Present

- · Writing some posts about lecture summary, paper review, some tips for developments.
- To share what I have studied with others and to remember it longer.

Monocular Depth Estimation with ORB-SLAM2

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

Personal Toy Project Sep. 2020 - Nov. 2020

- · I was curious about the performance of the recent depth estimation model.
- I used 'Monocular Depth Estimation with Transfer Learning pretrained MobileNetV2' model and applied to ORB-SLAM2 also compared with ORB-SLAM2(Monocular mode), ORB-SLAM2(RGB-D mode)
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository].

KCCV 2020 Korea computer vision society

Participant Aug. 2020

• Participated to know about the trend of Computer Vision

Using deep learning for data analysis and image processing (Basic)

Korea open source software

STUDENTS Jul. 2020

• Studied lectures which is related to the using Deep learning framework(Keras)

Runner Alarm System based on Deep Learning

BARAM (Robotics Academic Group)

Personal Toy Project Apr. 2020 - Jun. 2020

- I wanted to distinguish between walking children and running children with an object detection model.
- When children are running for an amount of time, a beep sounds.
- The source code related to this toy project is on my [Github repository].